Southern Tenant Farmers Union Research Files 5859
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers Union Research Files
1937-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Southern Tenant Farmers Union
Boyle, Louis
5859
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5722527
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 21, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Louise Boyle was born in Grand Forks, North Dakota in 1910, and passed away in December, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5204: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Speeches and Interviews 5204 mf: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Records on Microfilm 5859 P: Southern Tenant Farmers Union Photographs 6252 MB: Brian McNeill Collection of Southern Tenant Farmers Union Memorabilia
Farm tenancy, United States; Agricultural laborers, United States; Boyle, Louise.; Southern Tenant Farmers' Union.
5722527
- Boyle Louise - Correspondence (Legal issues), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Boyle Louise: Correspondence 2/15/95 -6/27/89, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Boyle, Louise - Notes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Boyle, Louise - Critiques on Text, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Boyle, Louise - Correspondence Updated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Boyle, Louise - Notes - 1982 visit to Tampa, Fla. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Boyle, Louise - Notes: Telephone Conversations with the Lawrence's: 1988-1984, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Boyle, Louise - Notes, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Boyle, Louise - Other Works: "Workers in Our Fields", 1939-1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Boyle, Louise - Other Work: Includes Now and Then and "Anthracite Coal Country", 1937-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Boyle, Louise - Photos + Commentary (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Boyle, Louise - Photos + Commentary (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Boyle, Louise - Photos + Commentary - Layout (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Boyle, Louise - Publications of 1937 Photos (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Boyle, Louise Research - Sources, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Boyle, Louise - Research - Sources, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Boyle, Louise - Research - Sources, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Boyle Louise - Research - Sources, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Boyle, Louise - Research - Sources, 1937-1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Boyle, Louise Research - Sources, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Boyle, Louise: Text - "Clothes" (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Boyle, Louise - Text "Black + White" (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Boyle, Louise: Text: "Cotton Of Policies + People" (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Boyle, Louise Text: "A Form of their own", 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Boyle, Louise: Text - "I'm a Union" (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Boyle, Louise - Text - "Looking Back" (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Boyle, Louise: Text - "Meeting at the Pinetree Schoolhouse" (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Boyle, Louise: Text - "Outdoor Union Meeting - Parkin Arkansas" (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Boyle, Louise - Text - "On The Way to the Lawrence's", 1937 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Boyle, Louise - Text - "Religion + Magic" (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Boyle, Louise - Text - "Bust Brothers Cotton Picker" (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Lawrence Family Tree, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Lawrence, Myrtle - Correspondence - 1937 (See Also Bx FF) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Letterhead - Southern Tenant Farmers Union, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Letterhead - United Cannery,, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Mitchell, H.L. - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Newspaper/ Magazine Clippings - 1985-1982, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Newspaper Magazine Clippings - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Newspaper/ Magazine Clippings 1981-1979, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Newspaper/Magazine Clippings - 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Photographs 1937 (xeroes) (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Mitchell, H.L. - Mean Things Happening in this Land Book Reviews, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Photographs - 1981-1982 (xeroes) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Robertson, Priscilla - Correspondence - 12/17/82 - 4/5/61, 1961-1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Robertson, Priscilla - Notes - 1983-1982, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Robertson, Priscilla - Correspondence 11/30/89 -12/24/82, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (early draft) (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Robertson, Priscilla "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (early draft) (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (early draft) (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Robertson, Priscilla "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" Critique - by Boyle, Louise (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (first Draft - 1937) (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" (Early Draft) (incomplete) (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937 (early Draft) (incomplete) (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937: A Chronicle of Change" (early Draft) (incomplete) (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937:" (early Draft) (incomplete) (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "A Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper" Critique - Temple University Press", 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Robertson, Priscilla - "Visit to an Arkansas Sharecropper in 1937" Early Draft - Incomplete (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Southern Tenant Farmer's Union - A Chronology, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Southern Tenant Farmer's Union - 48th Anniversary Celebration, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Southern Tenant Farmers Union - Releases, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Strikes (Box 1, Folder 63)